<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<!--
   
   Final Project
   Reiki By Jake
   Author: Jacob Fletcher
   Date: 11/22/2015   
   
   Sample RSS Headlines Feed


   Filename: headlines.xml
-->

<rss version="2.0">

   <channel>

      <title>Current Headlines From Reiki.org</title>
      <link>http://www.reiki.org/</link>
      <description>Reiki News Feed</description>

      <item>
         <title>My Reiki Story</title>
         <link>http://www.reiki.org/reikinews/MyReikiStory.htm</link>
         <description>It’s been 24 years since I first learned of Reiki and began experiencing
		 it’s miraculous power.  Since that time many changes have taken place in my life that 
		 were brought about by my association with this wonderful energy.
         </description>
      </item>

      <item>
         <title>Creating Prosperity with Reiki</title>
         <link>http://www.reiki.org/reikinews/Prosperity.htm</link>
         <description>"Prosperity and abundance are my Divine birthright." How long has it been
		 since you have made that statement? Has it been a month, a year, a decade…or never? 
		 Maybe intellectually you know that you live in an abundant universe, but do you FEEL 
		 it to be true?
         </description>
      </item>

      <item>
         <title>Reiki Dominoes … the Ripple Effect of Healing</title>
         <link>http://www.reiki.org/reikinews/Reiki%20Dominos.htm</link>
         <description>When I was a child, I was fascinated by dominoes, those little black 
		 rectangular pieces of plastic with the dots on them. I will admit I was never really
		 enthused by the actual game, but I loved to see them lined up, in curving, waving, 
		 undulating rows.
         </description>
      </item>

      <item>
         <title>Healing for the Highest Good</title>
         <link>http://www.reiki.org/reikinews/HighestGood.htm</link>
         <description>It was just about 17 months ago when I first met Chuck. I learned that
		 he had recently received a diagnosis of terminal cancer with about 6 months to live.
		 When I approached Chuck to volunteer to give him Reiki treatments I saw a vital man
		 with sparkling eyes and a wonderful smile. 
         </description>
      </item>

      <item>
         <title>What is Reiki, Who can Learn it?</title>
         <link>http://www.reiki.org/reikinews/WhatWhoReiki.html</link>
         <description>Reiki is a Japanese technique for stress reduction and relaxation that
		 also promotes healing. It is administered by "laying on hands" and is based on the idea
		 that an unseen "life force energy" flows through us and is what causes us to be alive. 
         </description>
      </item>

  </channel>

</rss>